[Music]
walk around and drive themselves over
the place over here
whatever
around the world thanks for the
tools or anything else you want
themselves
[Music]
whatever
you want to get
any of these
yeah get this one into
when i charge up the water and
everything else in first
and this will produce a gas i'll show
you in the middle of a blade
for a few bubbles
i'll lift this out if you want
the brown shoe on the outside is what's
coming out of the water you know i told
you
this one here doesn't have it but this
one here at the bottom
let's just bring it negative totally
square across
you have negative
the bottom
negative at the top
neutral in the center i mean positives
in the center
two neutrals
[Music]
different configuration of plates
negative
neutrals
positive
negative
underneath water
gas comes out
here which we'll see in a minute
glass bottle
fold through the middle down to the
bottom as a negative
place you're held in
neutrals
positive to that y you can see connected
brings a positive inside
negative plugs up underneath
positive clips to the outside line there
and then we'll show our experiment with
that in a minute
i'm gonna go along stylus um
fire extinguisher
negative in the top
neutral plating on the inside
okay uh choose
negative travels down the center right
to the bottom
explain about that soon
positive hooked up either here
here
or if you want the best gas hook it up
to the furthest point
around here or out there
you can release that and bring gas out
the front
you leave it off gas comes out here
vacuum gauge
or pressure gauge
plug that onto there
turn on this is a battery charger or you
can plug it up to a battery turn it on
you can read what pressure you got um
hook onto the front or here
you're on the front open that put a pump
on put a car on
vacuum and it shows your vacuum reading
on the
gauge as well
what vacuum you can pull in
this little cell here
it has
neutral plates on the inside
no chart no positive charge to it
whatsoever no power
negative through the bottom
this just bolts and separates you from
there it just goes into a car
and your car
doesn't have doesn't put any charge
positive or anything else to the outside
of that negative nature to the body and
that's all there is as anything going
through it there's a field
hook i'll know um
this goes into there
that screws under there that goes
through the firewall
that's aluminium you can use copper but
if you use copper you've got to put a
positive wire from the car to the
furthest point to get the gas out what
we want and it's not hydrogen oxygen
um
take it to the outside on aluminium
aluminium doesn't need a charge putting
under it it stores it in the metal
brings it out to the um into your motor
you've got to have a separate piece of
rubber on the end here to stop because
this here is positive even though it's
not connected but the gas inside the
water inside and everything else is
positive
so this is a positive
positive connection you can't connect
with the motor you've got to put a piece
of rubber in or else you get a dead
short to sell don't go
you gotta pull all the parts wash it all
out recharge water up put it back in
restart
and it gives you a problem
let's see how that works i'm recording
this um bottle here has neutral plates
in it it doesn't have any
um caustic or salts or anything else in
it it's plain water straight out of a
creek off a hill it has a neutral plates
it has positive outside negative
underneath as we see i'll now turn on a
battery charger
and
you'll see hallelujah now look down the
side work your way over the side you'll
see
that's hydrogen going downwards it won't
break the surface you see this vapor
coming off the top
that's possibly what's running the cars
it goes down
fills up it's plain water doesn't brown
doesn't dirty always got this paper
down below here if you look carefully if
you can pick it up something is being
drawn down from halfway
from here it's going up
from there up from there it's going
something else is being drawn down and
taken underneath can you see clearly
maybe
yeah i've got a vapor coming off the
surface
all that in there
is hydrogen
look at the top how did you might break
the surface
i'll turn it off and just keep your
thing going there and you'll see what
happens
power's turned off
clears it up
you lower your water put on tape if you
lower your water
to level with a plate or below it you
will not get any of that stuff down the
sides it'll just produce bubbles out of
each plate
if you want to see that i can tip that
top off and show you you won't get any
down the sides if you want to see
um
i'll just
you'll be able to see this
when i come back down you'll still see
it producing
production it's not what's coming back
up that will go off the place if you can
see through there
that produces gas for maybe an hour or
two after that's been on only for half a
minute
you charge that water up and charge
those plates up you have continuous
charge coming off that water as
electricity or bubbling and charge
none of those bubbles are breaking the
surface or sticking on the surface
they are gone
now we'll just
once you don't make a fiber out of me
we go back up again we have got our
water
below
the plates
put our stain on again
we can turn on
you want to come to the top now you will
see there's nothing happening down the
side but look what's happening in here
okay
now we're getting bubbles here
yeah
each one of those in turn i'll put a
little bit more water in you'll see
this is just plain water in the charge
it's got a bit of gunk in this one but
that's fine you just come up see it
when i go down the side you'll see it
still hasn't gone over the sides
i want to bring the water up to clear
the top
now as soon as the water goes over the
top
as the water goes over the top
[Music]
you'll see something breaking going down
then it start it comes back up
that is coming up you can see it clearly
now this is projection very well from
here down is drawing something down
under
now you want to look on the top you see
the bubbles
they've only come since we've
transferred it over
[Music]
keep the video going and hang onto
eardrums
hallelujah
and the aluminium which was in alum and
all the detergents they put in the water
to clean it up is still in this one
um
sorry wrong one that one goes there
that just clips to the outside as a
positive the neutrals as i showed you
before
this here just hooks up to negative
now that's just clicked onto the
negative cone i'll lift it out to show
you again just to be on the safe side
see
no connection
same thing again
that just goes into the negative
clip it on
you want to look in there you'll see
something
[Music]
the elevator
you reckon
the wind's blowing pretty strong here
too so it's blowing away the vapor
if you were to sniff that vapor would uh
just just nice just nice oxygen or
fiber gym what would it be
what we're doing now at least you must
poison yourself no it's not poison if
you look at the size what we're doing is
we are stretching the water out
the water has come up about that far so
far and it will keep coming up
and we'll lift and lift and then it'll
start forming large bubbles
and those large bubbles
what we can do what we're going to do is
we're going to turn the power off the
battery in a second
and those bubbles we're going to light
with a power turn totally off
just want to show you that these are
collecting into a larger stuff
for that
see them and this here is nice fine
beautiful clean white a bit of this
brown here is from the water i've had
some bad water lately
so
now
all right we'll turn the power off
we're going to match we'll leave it for
a minute
we're still there
it's just a match
you're right
what happened to the roof yep
now the water is dropped right back down
again
we stretch the water up it lifts
totally lifts up stands up
that's that one
that water in there is charged
if you can get that white stuff off the
top
now you'll be able to see that it'll
still produce
for
ages that has not been charged either
nothing's been on this morning just
follow you should be able to tell you
so now water but we've got our bubbles
each one of them is reliable
and if you can see across which not
water is not deep enough you can see
across it'll still be producing gas off
those neutral plates
now whether you can pick it up
it's only fine but now that's pushing 14
and a half pounds
per square inch of atmospheric pressure
to get any of those bubbles off or
produce anything
all we do is hook a vacuum to it
you remove the 14 and a half pounds per
square inch
and then you put out
not hydrogen or oxygen you put out
whatever
and that's what runs cars and it comes
off like i don't know what
okay
this is a keg for charging
charging the water i don't use this for
anything except for charging
positive outside
negative
and top and bottom
positive in the inside
center
outside this
charge
you want to try this is plain water
which is in here which comes straight
from the creek
and try to come up an inch
further so you can see the bubbles
now we'll turn the power on
and instantly the water starts to rotate
rotation
waits a minute bills of charge
no bubbles yet
as soon as it's charged now our bubbles
come from nowhere no white stuff no
clearing beautiful bubbles stick on the
surface
it's plain fresh water straight out of
the tap
that's how long it's been on and
charging the first few bubbles
that's with it on
now we'll leave it go for a few minutes
because they're not the bubbles what i
want to show you
what they've done is went from the
center straight out to the outside
we're going to get a bit of muck in this
because the water is polluted up here
the better the water the fresher and
cleaner the water the better this is
this is charging the water and if you're
talking about sewage or dirty water or
pollutants in water
this is what it does to it
it totally cleans your water pulls them
off
separated you can put a it's not
underneath it it's only on the surface
brings it to the surface you can get a
different bucket strain it all off take
it off throw it away you've got clean
beautiful water
that's really yucky
power is off
there's still production going very well
off this
this is charged well
no charge on
oops
flame went out
doesn't matter there's no charge on
ah
come here
louder getting better
getting better bottom
that water is cold
they will get bigger and bigger and
bigger
and they come up i've had them that big
you can leave them all day as long as
they don't burst they won't burst
they'll sit there all day
that gives you a surface tension
that's why they're sitting there surface
tension everything else you'll do you
can take this you want everything else
you do
everything what comes off there we'll
break the surface and it's gone there's
no bubbling there's no nothing and
nothing stays there this is charged
water this is the only time and anytime
else that you'll get
bubbling
waits a minute
now water's charging up now
comes through
the very first bubbles are lightable and
blow your head off
you charge that water
leave it going for a short period of
time and get a good charge into the
water you can see what's coming off
they're clean they're clear there is
totally nothing beautiful in that water
the more you leave it to charge the
better it gets
those bubbles
they will stay there
all day all tomorrow
you come out tomorrow
you hit the um
any one of those bubbles you hit them
with a match and
and do you notice it's getting louder
sure what your ears drums doing
because mine are absolutely ringing like
because they're totally in place
and if you got on camera there was no
flame no orange flame no nothing
totally
now
the bubbles come after the flash
they're still there
[Music]
no charge on now and it's still charging
it's still going to bring bob off here
i haven't charged that it's getting
louder and louder you want me to leave
that on for say
um 10-15 minutes
you will not stand in here because every
one of these sheets of tin on this roof
and everything will be shaping with the
sound you'll have to hold your eardrums
it'll go through your hand i've done it
your body will feel a thump
not against it your body will feel a
thump
the ground down here will thump
shake
that is plain straight nothing in it you
want me to drink it
if you want to try the straight finger
and feel the slip
there is no costing
just pleasure this is for you
i'm not guaranteeing that every car will
run straight away off this gas the
little escort took a day and a half
that's a cast iron motor it had to put
positive gas into the manifold and into
the motor and totally changed it it took
a week
after we took the manifold and carved
the off and the gas off it took a week
before i could change the timing back
and get it to run smooth again on air
and petrol
a week after to get it back out of the
middle
now
you use this oogies up i know it runs on
the rover the leylands the escort a
holden motor
a falcon motor
a forklift gas forklift
many others can't think of all now but
some cars with a negative charge in the
motors takes
a certain time for these not hydrogen or
these ions or these positives to get in
pollute the metal change it from
negative
to positive then it runs
this car here now will show you later
it will run straight off because the
pollutants are still in the motor
they're in the manifold they're in the
carburetor
so i'll show that later anyway
so and that gas there you saw
has no
color when you light it
it is if you want to if your eardrums
can pick it up there totally implosive
pulls your eardrums very loudly doesn't
it
no fine no nothing and it is not hiding
in that stuff
there is nothing in the water i've
drinking it there's tattoos there's no
slippers
and all these two exactly the same if
you put costic or indigos into those
waters within that period of time any of
these will be red hot
with the charge and the plate and the
stuff that's coming off they'll all turn
hot
they stay cold
water in about there
and this is gas reserve this is a welder
and this is a cutter
and this is also a running car that's
been run this one's run a car that one
included
the escort included i've now filled it
full of fresh water or
fall is brought down straight he knows
what it is right to the brimming top
i'll now take
the charge
i'll put it on
positive outside
negative hose that goes inside like i
described before
i'll turn the power on i want you to get
close here because you will see with
charging water will lift
expand out
it's now on
[Music]
clean white bubbles have a look at the
tension on this it's standing up quarter
of an inch or more the water above
the surface
just for fun
we've got these bubbles to trickle over
down here
they're on there
you see
this is plain straight water
oops that's a plain straight dead match
you're watching
this is power on
i don't have power on
i'll let them go down and build up
this is dead straight plain water
i'll just get a little bit of charge
into the um
into the water
oh yeah
gonna leave them sit on there they build
up they'll stay on there like they do on
the keg
on there they stay on
and he's not off the ceiling
bubbles that charge the water playing
water running over his charge
hit it again if you're right
[Applause]
it's charging you see
it's getting pretty good in it
is this about as good as your balloon
was less
the bubbles are gone you want to have a
look in
others are gone
water's shrunk back down again
okay
see they're collecting in big
blobs in there
right i'm gonna light it god dude you're
right
no power on
okay
that's that one
i'd like to get some onto the surface
down here this is plain straight out
water
that now the water is down to there
you've just looked
the water is now stretching
stretching
it's coming up
and we'll just wait you'll see the
bubbles in here if you want if we're
hopefully
it's sitting there now
and in a few seconds
it should pour over the top
come on
it's got to build up what i just set off
in there
here it comes
have a look at the action if you like if
you want to come in closer
[Music]
if you're wondering this is dead plain
water
and
pull from there to there this plate
turn around
look at the charger
we're pulling less than 20 amps
when i charge this up and leave it
overnight
we will pull two or four amps only
and do better than that
now
i'll add a little bit more so you know
so all that plain water
let's see
and i'm going to go over the side we'll
try and get something down here
to stay on there it's on tim of that
[Music]
i'll show you something else for this
again in a few minutes but we'll get a
bubble
[Applause]
that one had a yellow flame
why
it had a yellow flame this is on paint
all right yeah
[Music]
on neutral plates
what happens is
ordinary electricity spirals and goes
right to the bottom and gurgles up
comes up with the bubbles
on neutral plates the current goes in
and does a total
right-hand bend in every direction of
these
straight out sideways
so what happens is if you inject the
negative in at the top positive doesn't
matter it's right around
if you inject the negative in at the
bottom
it does this
all the way up to the surface
everything's trying to get to the
surface
now
if you just put it into the top it
doesn't work the full length of the way
down so you have to put your negative in
at the bottom
in this blue one i've injected at the
top but i've run a wire straight down
through the center of the negative and
put it on the bottom
and this is like an insulated wire yeah
insulated wire
like this it's insulated all the way to
the bottom and then it's hooked onto the
under the bottom right at the bottom and
then it works its way all to the top if
you look at this in through the top i've
done it you don't get half the
production half the bubbles you will
produce hydrogen and you only get a few
little bubbles nothing
you got to do it in certain positions
this here is totally by all rights and
figures by putting neutral plates across
that cuts down to buggery on each one it
goes through it cuts down halves the
current input so by right plain water
should not produce one single bubble
nothing
and you saw what that does well that's
right there and now i can increase that
three fold over
by doing something else
outside
positive
the one we had connected to negative
before
we will now
hook up
to positive
so the center
is positive
the outside is positive negative you
mean positive higher yeah
i see what you mean that's positive here
yeah
i bring this
to
the
center
wire center one
i then
put
negative
to the center
of those tubes
you want to see three times production
off the same plate have a look
[Music]
watch the other bubbles are look at the
vapor look at the coloring
you're watching how quick it is
[Music]
you got it
you watch
see how quick it is
let's just go into the center
that is not the way i do it
that charges your water awful quick
you can add charge to it if you want
this is plain straight water
don't know why there must be a stuff in
the water it's called 10 amps we need to
pull half an amp on this
we'll grab some um
plain
water we'll build up because i always
have the water right down
we could all burst on the
water to see the same he said mama runs
a car
has not been charged to put on this
morning it's plain straight water
doesn't have anything in it yet no
charge no nothing i'll drink the water
you all know what the water was
[Music]
pushes it pushes out the water and
everything else it doesn't want even
under vacuum it'll pull down to where it
wants won't use any from there
you go as far as you like on this stuff
if your water is below where she can
pull any down a hose
and you will not use
around australia if you want won't use
any water come back still got the same
water
if you go above
where it's going to vacuum it out or
push it out you will use what it pushes
out or use what will come out under
vacuum or splash
after that you won't use any
you can keep topping it up as far as you
want whatever you want to do on top
build it up draw it out through back in
and it's been on for as long as you
heard so far
[Applause]
pull the eardrums if you want to
very well
let's see
still lifting yeah
if you put your thumb over
very strange thing happens
the bubbles
go back
to the water
see
you want to come up close and have a
look
i'll put my thumb over i'm going to
build up bitter press come over and have
a look in i got i got you guys
right then where i can watch
yeah
and we're getting a pretty good pressure
aren't we oh yeah
and well how many how many tubes have
you got inside one another there
uh one negative two neutrals one
positive outside oh yeah like four four
yeah if your gas is no good
and you want to increase the performance
of implicit gas near any girls do that
let it build up for a sec
take your finger off
here we go again
yellow flying
want to change the gap
all you do is put your finger back over
it again or
add
plain straight
water
[Applause]
play bubbles
[Music]
normally
without this fluid mort their cell is
cold
without the pollutants and everything
else i usually get half an amp on this
but this water's gone bad in the last
couple of days
this cell here yesterday was pulling 25
in
i'll let it settle overnight it's
polluted got some of the fluids out it's
now pulling in believable i might put
some charging leaves tomorrow we will go
down on plain water down to half an amp
and i'll put out the same gas but more
potent that is plain straight water a
few bubbles there very very very hope
as soon as you get the minerals and
you've got a dirty water you've got a
hydrogen you've got a yellow flame
you've got less bang no ear pole you've
got a pressure
you come to plain water clean good plain
water clear bubble clear everything else
very banging very implosive ear poise
anyway i'll leave that
if i feed back
if i turn on
i can put 60 amps in
and stay the same box
that'll charge your battery if you want
i can go for a small
bike battery right up to one to up to
five batteries if you want
it's yeah 10 years
about 10 volts for me yeah 11 gold
and 60.
but that's got that's the supercharger
[Music]
yeah in water or the sulfuric acid on
the plates
and the sand is pulling heat and heats
and heats it in
hmm
oh
yeah but that would charge up real
well i'll show you
we saw a minute ago
that we had um
very low
voltage 12 volts from everything else on
this see what we've got there
we can plug this on
now i've set it on boost
and you watch what i can put in
i can put in
55 volts 55 60 volts yeah i'm going to
see what i'm putting into the cell that
one after it's been charged
from the charge
[Music]
now
if i
[Music]
this is a good machine i can set it to
anywhere i want
i've got it open so i can change things
and get out whatever i want
we want to see we can go over to this
one again
and put it on
we can put in voltage whatever voltage
you want go to boost
we can go to
54 57 volts
same goes same everything else
you'll get out the same way
don't care about voltage
the more voltage i put in the less i
pull on the way i'll set up my plates
the less voltage i put in
the more i pull yeah
that's if i want to produce hydrogen
oxygen or gas or bubbles or anything
else but that's not what i do that's not
what i want to do
go back to one and i do worse
let's go wherever i want to set it up
or i can go just an ordinary battery do
the same
if i put it on charge and go through dry
i could put water in the in the car it
should be in on the other video about me
that's still to the top
now when i put this into there
and as for you i'll put a bit of charge
into it
now
you'll see the bubbles go into there or
the cell sends it builds up the charge
in here bubbles will go into there
they're very explosive
they're through a flash arrester if we
can light them first off doesn't matter
that water should as the charged gas
goes into it should expand that water
out which is plain river water and pour
it over the sides
it charge expands the water
as soon as we get the bubbles coming
through
we'll see if they are lightable straight
off
the same
cell doesn't matter
different gas thing there what you want
all together
[Music]
straight through
just lift this we did nothing just put
the top on
but what's coming off there
cannot be lit by
[Music]
there we go
now we're changing over to implicit gas
what's the plane and the match
you know some of the other
so you've got three different kinds of
gases there already yeah one with the
yellow flame one where the knees places
and throws water at you and the other
one which is not lightable
all in
all the time
that's what happens
where you going
knock down
no pressure in that or anything else is
still going
keeps
going funny thing about all this is
every one of these
with plain water
with the power turned off
has twice the band gas with the power
turned off as with pounds
hmm
yeah some of these are loud
with the power
yeah
more bang with the power off with no
power going into it this is more banging
up
now
what we've got here is a pressure gauge
this pressure gauge it's a vacuum and a
pressure gauge and what i've set out i
can't get back up it is 10 below
north
oh yeah
but
and we had in places gas which goes into
the water and throws it out and does not
have a flame
on here
with an open lid
i turn the power off for three seconds i
turn it off
i have
when i light
that air rushing in
i turn the power back on three seconds
turn it off
i put a match to the top i get
air coming out
i turn the power back on i turn it back
off again three seconds again i now blow
everything to smithereens
just goes
boom
three different gases and you can see
the three different gases there by each
bubble
in the cell here with an open lid i get
implosive exhaust and then
explosion or implosion actually it's
implosion because i've stuck this lid
here totally down into there
three times now and i've got to knock
them back out on an open cell i'll pull
the center plate to clean up that far
out of the water as the implosion went
and i threw electricity right around
this whole shed off to sell when it went
and i'm not going to do that for you now
because i've already been cut and
shocked and inflamed
now we're up to 100 or actually 120
because of 10 overseas
now
on this i just put a
away
i've got a microsoft steel cover
[Music]
you see what one bubble does
now
to like this i have to cover my hands
because all my hairs and everything else
total
totally
non-existent afterwards
actually i'll get a bit of paper
cut some stuff together
this balloon is going to do one of three
things
one is
it's going to implode and flame and turn
the balloon inside out and in rushing
air it's going to take every hair off me
or everything else the second thing
that's if we got the implosive gas
straight off
secondly if we've got hydrogen there
will be a big bang and a yellow flame
and explosion
thirdly
there'll be another thing which
if it's there you'll see
i can change the gas
three different gases i can get off that
cell to do whatever i want
you still you're still there joe
that had a yellow flame to it okay
that was either jim
first off second time i'll do it
i just every if you pick it up on there
there's a very big shed and every one of
the sheep that's in the shed just shook
oh battle yeah yeah right
and it pulled my eardrums
and so on but my eardrums are still here
so that was
um explosion hydrogen as well as a
little bit of inflation get the other
stuff
i don't even know where the balloon went
okay well we got this is what's left of
the balloon
fragmented
and we've got a frequency in it which is
hydrogen that's a low negative wave
when you get the implosive it is 100
it's ripped
yeah it looks fine it's bubbly
absolutely
next time i blow up a balloon you saw
first off i said before first off you
get one gas second off you get another
gas third off you get another gas
so that's how it works i don't know why
but when you get the gas what you want
you can test to buy a balloon to see
what you've got but what you do what
you've got now
you've got to know what comes next
and then you can draw that gas off if
you don't want that gas you put a
balloon on you blow it up you can
finally get the next guest fine that's
which yeah we'll do it again if you want
i think we'll save our eardrums
um
give you a better degree
[Music]
altogether yeah different bang
different gas
we have all the balloon here now this
time
and this time we don't have
virtually any
frequency
now the next guess i know what i've got
and i'm not going to light one of them
because the next one will turn the
balloon inside out fragments for me and
pieces and foam and pull our eardrums
and i've done it i've smashed these
lights before so i can pull them out of
the roof first
and these in the inside the balloon are
dry
the next gas that runs the car
when the balloon is fragmented the
balloon is turned inside out this is the
way that balloon was then
right way up
the balloon is fragmented to a million
pieces and it's turned inside out and it
is soaking wet
it's condensed the rain yeah it's
condensed rain it's made rain
let's go down the next gas does that
powerful i can't even feel that amount
of the balloon
if i can find
the balloons
all this doesn't do nothing
we've got um
sulphur powder
urea
blue stain
um
nitram never used that one that's
explosive very
nicely all right for the black quarries
we've got magnesium sulfide
products
um
[Music]
is available straight off the counter in
the chemist shopping yeah by card
by card stoner in water
produces with a charge on a producer's
oxygen
bicarb soda in plain water
use a magnet the north end of a magnet
turn it anti-clockwise produces hydrogen
oh yeah
potassium nitrate
i cannot make this stuff go off with
anything
potassium nitrate except for the way the
scientists do it at school they teach
the kids to go blow mailboxes apart yeah
yeah you make you you make big bangs out
of them
or on the forex borax
i've tried through every one of these
things before i have tried every one of
them i can produce hydrogen i can
produce oxygen i can produce lightable
stuff non-lightable i cannot produce
anything but runs a car i cannot produce
anything but puts out anything but a big
yellow flame and you have to pull a uh
you pull up to maybe 60 amps
to get any bubbles
and then the cell instantly gets hot no
matter what you use
in here
happens to be
a carbide powder
you want to have a drop of water today
you get acetylene yeah before the
produce is settling you had a drop of
water that you get off a big bomb yeah
that's right how did your peroxide of
130 volume
um
what is it
never use it brand new
that's all i have that's all i've tried
there's balloons everywhere around the
floors
which have different
that's paint i've often tell i've
totally fragmented paint as well
now
i know i can do this
anyway
high positive frequency
comes around it's out of mind
see that little hook
that little hook is my gene line if you
know what a gene line is
my children
to tell if they're my children you can
do a blood test or you can do a test
with a balloon
my children if i get them to blow up a
balloon i've got a daughter and a son
and i get them to blow off a balloon
their frequency out here will be a
little bit different but that there is
100 identical and you can grab their
balloon and sit it over that if he does
one you do one anybody else does one
they will all be different you'll never
get one to sit back over there unless it
is from the same gene
remember
and i've done this with thousands of
people and i can prove it now if he
blows one up
and i put a bit of spit
on my finger and i touch him
sure what i get what he gets in the
balloon when he blows it up is his
frequency and two
of mine
two of these mines why i don't know but
two of those are my children being
transferred over through the asses spit
off my tongue onto my finger and touch
him for one split second
and if you're a negative field person
and i just come along put a bit of spit
on and i touch your hand you put blow up
a balloon you now can blow it up where a
minute ago as a negative person you
couldn't even light it you'd burn a hole
through and go fizz down
then now you can light it
now
i've got balloons if you have
if you have a sickness or a disease or
anything else
it's a low negative field and it'll put
a wave or a striker point
leaves no
high frequency pitches little m's
i can hold that depends on where you
blow it up i can hold it up to your body
and if you have a disease from halfway
down and you blow the balloon up aiming
downwards the rip across the balloon
like that will show it up and i can tell
you that you without even knowing you i
can tell you that you've got a disease
from there down i can tell you where to
go to cancer i can tell you what you've
got out of the air out of your own mouth
now on quantum here i've done this for
about four years
on quantum about um
oh what was it about six months ago
there is a man
who is going to take the police
breathalyzers
and he has taken them now and on them
there is a frequencies
big high squares he's put them on on a
computer thing now in people with known
cancers
breathing into these he has found one
little striker like this different than
everybody else
with no cancers so he's going to take
from their breath
make up these machines which are going
to foam and tell you whether you've got
a cancer or a sickness or anything else
in front of them now there was a guy
coming to me i will get this on dave
there's a guy coming to me shed here the
other day i've never met him before he
heard what i was doing a man brought him
here
um
i didn't know him never met him didn't
know there was something wrong with him
i got him to blow up a balloon the same
as i just did air out of his mouth took
a fair bit to light it when it did when
he blew it up he held down like that and
blew up
he blew the balloon up
he buys him mad and he's had it for
three years
he dropped his pants he missed you here
to show us he said how did you know
i said i didn't but your balloon showed
up in frequency in the way that you did
if you blow the balloon up i would have
looked at this part
incredible
the thing is what you can
record yeah
different guys again
the piece of water
oh
still got the same
that was hydrogen
see the yellow flame before
there's two different ones one out with
yellow flames one in which fits the
water
i think
[Music]
all right
gary
[Music]
turned right off and everything goes and
i can't i was down under 1500 until we
just come back from the drive and we're
in this island
north
totally normally
[Music]
you don't want to come back
so
[Music]
hey quick get down there
on the bench all right
playing the hill
before
what
there's no people in there now put it
before it slowly out you see that you
saw where the pepper was before didn't
you yeah well there's nothing there's
nothing in the uh in the filter there
now
should
the cell if you've got the sound gun
what the cell does is when you hook it
up and the cell starts to cut in
and if you do have fuel on there
carburetor fights the running power
until she does it
you can't get it on air and petrol down
under 500 as you know now the thing is
down onto idle
you know and she drives the petrol clean
back down the line and back to the tank
and you won't have nothing in your bowls
or carving or anything else and that's
how
so you know what you got
you know what you haven't got
[Music]
it's
he's trying to take over
[Music]
oh
starting to stop the air gun
[Music]
what am i doing
cutting the fuel
if you screw that in
will you feel you screw that out
we don't get fuel
[Music]
lining up with the uh
cables and that
i'm sure he's good at big enough
what
big enough one
i thought
don't worry
jordan
chris
well
i reckon we were
i reckon we were totally on gas and
there was nothing in the bowl
there's nothing in here
and we just chat everything changed up
high
so if i wrap this around
this is what we did at the furthest
point on that
[Music]
he went right up over seven thousand
oh
a little bit below 7 000 and changes
pitch
[Music]
cool
accelerator either i'm not even
in the gutter
[Music]
break this back and i'll get it to come
up
before you could come up here the rover
then come up here and talk to you and
wouldn't even scream up here what this
was doing the other week before ron
killed it she'd come up here eight
thousand rounds you screamed straight up
over the top yeah you don't change
you're just it
is that's deep
it went up what two thirds of the way in
top gear
and then i let it dive right down below
to 500 and i changed
i had to go back if i would have went
back one gear i would have pulled up
there in third
you know she would have made it
[Music]
uh
yeah and on the game
[Music]
i'd like to see if i can change the time
and apply
oh yeah
[Music]
now
at least 10 kilometers now since we took
the fuel pipe off
[Music]
down to half rev a half tank you just go
down to empty
and this is a fourth or fifth frame
four fourth gauge we put in this there's
a branch thinking new one we put in here
now they still play out their last short
time and then they play after so what he
was doing instead of his trip meter to
see what he can get
well for the amount of water that you've
got in your unit here you shouldn't have
to worry about fueling up for the next
uh what 25 000 kilometers
that's incredible
and see the motors different noise isn't
it oh it's as smooth as that
[Music]
it's got a nice durable to it now which
she's not dying so much a second before
with pedro she grew
up sorry
more parents
even i'm not there she didn't have that
before either did it
[Music]
see thirds you die out a little and then
you could pick up in over half rest can
you start
[Music]
well she's a wicked little motor now
not a papa smoke nothing
but you don't even get you're not even
getting a myth of petrol vapor you know
what i mean you're not getting that
black food well you know
once you'll get in your car you give it
a rev you'll get a black suit first now
well there's no petrol there to make
sure yeah but i mean you know before it
yeah when the fire is uneven you know
you know
what do we got here and actually
[Music]
or something
there's no
noise verbal
you know
[Music]
responsive as what it was but
well we had
we had an island and then before at 8
and um
before and then we transferred over
you know we took up a run yeah um out
the road
and i've screamed at the top of you
there we made you send it right around
you know you flapper out
when we get back to the shed
what i'll get you to do before i shut it
down i'll get you to just
take a video as you come into the um you
know down the drive yeah i'll get into
the shed and i won't shut it down
and then i'll
hit the accelerator
and use
yeah so what we're doing too we're
pushing 7 000 revs instantly straight
out without any hesitation and we're
pushing all of us yeah
but that's the car
[Music]
that's
that's what i call a fight imprint if i
saw that with somebody else
brother
[Music]
wow that is that is truly amazing
what i might even do is when we get up
to your home
[Music]
see this one here
how do you that white one you know oh
yeah
[Music]
me yeah so if i turned off i'll see what
she does and the lower gears see if
she'll crack out
any further you know what i mean
or whether
whether or not we are
we need it on or off with running
or not
[Music]
all right
oh yeah people having the entertainment
stream
[Music]
bangkok
hmm
[Music]
all right
way up against the start
uh only twice
this is just to show you
okay so the inner cylinder is negatively
charged
then we have three neutral charge
uncharged uh
plate from the outside one so
you're looking inside now there's
nothing right
looking
and you should be able to pick up this
vapor
can you yeah that radro because that's
not steamed
unless you have white hydrogen oxygen
combination from electrolysis
oh no no you've actually put neutral um
neutral water in
plain water yes
see your bubbles do not stay in the
surface
they're gone
anything yep okay now this is raining
basically rain water
okay now i will go over the plate
instantly look what happens
yeah but now watch
you um let me see down the sides now
is this water's
fitted
yeah
that water's not charged yet and see
look this is our bubbling which just
breaks away it's gone
and those you don't have to hold your
eardrums and just don't work
if you look now you will find something
has gone to here
and it turns around and comes back
where's that rubber one um
if i don't touch anything
i'll show you
you can see it off this yeah
something's drawn down this goes to
there and returns
and that's not charged water yet that's
not the way i do it that's just ordinary
ordinary yeah
okay
now
if you go on the plate nothing happens
out here if you go above a fraction
everything happens out here the water
you end up with a magnetic field
twisting yeah
okay now we're pulling out the minerals
water in the
in the water here see these
i want to get rid of some of those thank
you
okay now i'm going to go positive center
and positive
outside
right this is how i charge the water
to
what would you call it either um chill
to um
give me circus tension
anyone have a gay right now
these don't break now
right
these are a little different
yeah i gotta
[Music]
do that
all right
no that's just clean the um all right
cling the glass right between your face
you said well
explain it
back to the same way again
let's get rid of all the contamination
now let me turn her on
all right
what was the current beforehand i don't
know um 20
about 20 amps in there look at this
white stuff in there now look so we're
down to uh about five seconds
right
very much fine
now our bubbles are staying there see
see they're not breaking like they used
to just like this water yeah
okay
and when we charge this up
you see as you start to use over but
you're watching out there you're
clearing here yeah you
[Music]
that goes there
something else from there you'll watch
it a little clear one goes from i'll get
out the light can you
shoot
you can can you see them
totally different yes
i'm looking at topics totally totally
different stuff
looks like an ounce of felt down there
looks like an alka seltzer
yeah
[Music]
out
um the metal on the electrodes cause the
problem
yeah it eats the chromium off and
these were chrome
they're only pretty neat keeps eating it
all yeah
all that water is just straight dead
water and everything else
these are all right for now because
that's just been put in haven't been
charged i usually take it out of the
input into there
yep no yellow flame
this needs some of these waters need a
bit of a kickstart you know
over hours
and produce
all the time for hours
yeah
good that's production continuous yeah
side
i've negatively charged some water
and then i took some other water and i
positively charged it
and on the meter she only reads like
that did you know maybe
one amp or something 12 oz
put the two together into a container
should pull 60 in
two different yeah
okay
now
all right let's see if there's any
difference in that water what we put in
before
going a bit more
ten
that's well yeah feet difference in the
water
those two waters there's two different
waters
this is the only way hooking them up
this way is the only way i can charge my
water so see the bubbles and they're not
breaking the surface are they no right
right you saw it before they just come
up and they're gone yeah they don't stay
there
okay this has been charged yeah you want
to hear this stuff
we'll let it go for a second in this
container too to get the um polarization
right for this cell because it's been
polarized to this so we'll give it a
polarized to this now we're going to
fill it up a bit more
and if it doesn't work this way
i um put my hands over and build up a
little bit of pressure uh well not so
much for the field over the top with a
positive feel over top
and then my bubbles can come about that
big
just one bubble
pretty good stuff yeah
the bubble formation is it's almost as
it's got detergent and they're sticking
together the bubbles
does that start to get bigger yeah
well
um
now hold it over see
you pretty right yep
surface tension straight away
there is something they say that white
milky stuff
that's hiding
and this stuff here isn't
this is with the power on yeah
the water from around the creek and that
was filled rocky creek dam and remember
here
okay power off
bubble's still there
watch
[Applause]
here's a different resonance
high pitched
cows and as far as i can figure out big
colors aerials all the gear
they'll come and sit out the front of
the other side of the road here and
they'll watch india they'll listen i
know they'll listen because um
my son and i have been the shed here and
we haven't been in eye contact with them
and we know that they were sitting there
for hours watching while we've been
playing here and then um your son and i
have decided to go out there and see who
they are
and they haven't even spotted us and we
haven't spotted them we start to walk
out and they shoot off and another car
comes
and takes its place a different sort of
car a different color
you go in the car and go anywhere
they'll follow you
even when i work around the corner doing
a bit of mechanical work at this shop
i've had a fellow sitting over on the
other side corner
and i went over south lismore to a drop
off ahead
and um this car with all the aerials and
everything else followed me all the way
over there i reversed him
and i saw him i had a feeling about him
i just drove straight back out again he
was going to park up the road a bit
further and he followed me i went around
the back streets all the way
crisscrossed and he followed me all the
way reversed back in and just hopped out
of the car and he kind of complicated
him
and then i took off again and come back
to work do you feel it's a police or
special forces or whatever well i had
the number plate taken to the rta
the guy who followed me over south i
took the number plate and i took it to
the rta to have him
check down on the on who it is and they
told me
that i couldn't find out who it is
because the number plate was silent
just i said what does that mean
he said if you flip a solo phone number
you cannot have information to that
number place
that's the relationship
butchering down to 39 sizes under
which would make it about a 93 correct
right
what we've done is um virtually 69.
oh going down to 69. sorry i'll just
show you here
which are jet drills
these are your soldered up ones
get tight
sort of fix your mark yep
fine
okay now the size what the 140s were
originally they're the 140s
what they originally were is not on this
set of dials it's bigger again yeah
so i'll come down to buggery
yeah good
okay well for the video
until you get started
just now putting in the
smaller jets
into the carburetor now why are we doing
this for sir
can you help blame for a start
if you want to run a mix you
can if you um
and that's not really the main reason
but to show you on petrol now without
touching any rest of the car that's
driven in here
to show it with a smaller jet and
everything else that um we now when we
touch the accelerator she will
cut out soon well either little idle but
touching it to open up the secondary
throat won't run on the fuel what's in
here yeah then with this fuel in here
and the cell on
we will start the vehicle and we'll show
that the thing will rev over 7000 revs
when i set the timing to suit
see gas now and uh then
we'll disconnect this line here and bang
it up
and that's our fuel input
and we will um let the car be sit here
on fuel and run totally out of fuel
right and you can try your hardest to
get it going yep and then what we'll do
then is um we won't put any more petrol
into it we will then hop into it
and we'll whirl it over yup
and we'll start it on the gas by itself
and i'll show you by the taco you can
sit in the back and take the taco on
your machine there and you'll still see
it
going well over 7000 revs with the um
petrol totally disconnected fine how's
that sounds excellent
and for a four-cylinder engine what sort
of advance do we need 47 to 50 degrees
advance before top dead that's on this
one on this
engine yeah fine
when the gas starts to go into a motor
there's probably about three or four
when you first initially hook it up
uh times that you have to re-advance the
timing
as the gas starts to get in your timing
isn't so far advanced
if you take a run up the road you might
go say
a mile within that mile or so you'll um
you may get out and change your timing
two or three times till
the um
you're matching the motor to suit the
gas and as the gas gets in there in that
distance
to um
align all the
structure to the suited gas
you may get the best performance you may
type move the timing three times till
you get it to the 47.
on an aluminium motor oh yeah this is
the energy
this is a cast iron motor and the cast
iron motor takes a period of time to get
it through does the cast iron
or all the aluminum become magnetic at
any time
not that i've found out that the um
not in the magnetics by taking a
magnitude or anything else to it but i
believe it's a different kind of
magnetism
your water in here if you put coolant in
your radiator um your coolant disappears
don't know where but the water doesn't
disappear the smell of the the rubber
and the you know normal heat water
disappears when you get it running
these here
run cold
exhaust water with the back of your hand
yeah cold
we had a run in this
um
a few weeks back in we were early on a
scorching hot day and i drove 12
kilometers
with the just the gas on
and this radiator cap that button in the
center there
had ice on it
and we had
the government's
aggregate
agricultural college they have a
mechanical course out there my son works
i've done a mechanical course there
i drove from south westmore out to there
to pick him up in this car
and um
i just hopped up full of water hopped
into it drove out to there
hard run on a boiling hot day
pulled up
got the head of the workshop to come out
pulled the bonnet checked the foaming
radiator and on that button there was
ice he put his hand on the radiator and
put his hand on the joystick and he said
[Laughter]
we now know what it is we didn't know
what was before excellent
excellent that's good i'm pleased about
that so he can verify that and so on
now
this here has got those gaps in it's
your life as soon as you start the
accelerators you'll just cut out that's
just petrol with 30
nine sizes or something smaller yeah
down to 69.
61 sizes
[Music]
right
oh
would you agree with that all right
we're just uh hitting the cell
down into the hole in the floor if you
come this way you'll be able to see all
right we're coming around
[Music]
there's a hole in the floor
uh
you get it
too bad uh nearly nearly
well
okay
just a hole in the floor
to um screw on your negative on the
bottom of the cell oh yeah
okay
you want to undo that yeah
let's just
go through that
[Music]
over there
are you going with the big shifter
either you might
need a um
i don't need a welder one
all right joe yeah
[Music]
lay yeah under here and put the wing nut
on there
yep
also negative
and that negative goes to the center
electrode is that right
now
right
yep
you know this just
plugs up under there
i think we think this will be that's all
right
this is the fine tuning that's it
so we're all connected we're all
connected no no that's not you want to
do the cable uh the hose
we'll um hose paint you want to do that
not like that gas
you can have a torrent you will not
light it with nothing
what you've got to do is the metal clip
on the front of the cigarette lighter
you have to scrape it onto a positive
[Music]
bit dark down
you were here
[Music]
so
this is a positive wire yep
that will be connected to the
intake
manifold
drawing from the cell
so that it remains positive
the reason that we don't want it to
touch anything
on the outside
[Music]
when the gas doesn't go in there's a
hair whisker
here
line from where it is
normal on people you can grab it did you
do that
when you get this gadget all by yourself
you can't even move it a week
[Music]
so what we're doing is running on fuel
uh hydrocarbon fuel petrol
to
prime and charge the cell
at which time we'll shut the fuel off
and be totally on
h particles
[Music]
okay
yep
[Music]
next phase of the trick is
this part of the trick is get the heel
off
get the fuel off
[Music]
yeah
started then turned off real
thank you quick where the fuel is coming
up from the fuel pump
[Music]
i'm not going to guarantee because this
hasn't been running for a while
yeah i'm going to guarantee it's going
to go straight forward
for you
there seems to be a lot more regarding
shuttle energies and energies we don't
even know about uh
in effect
uh charging
before when i tied this up
i've had the gas in there running for a
while and then i've um
you know you stay in there for nearly a
week or more
so i can just go in that time and hit it
back on again
lately
lately we've had this off now for what
probably
nearly six weeks yeah
we're in a situation if
if uh our friends caught by the police
with this apparatus on
see you later well yeah i think so
typically uh
when we come across to
our other friend's story about the guy
that got the bullet through the head
right
come sloping
[Music]
all you do is screw that inward
and we're going to let it run until she
totally runs out fuel
[Music]
whatever's coming off the cell normally
this would run out without the salon
need to run out of probably by hand
[Music]
but
the other thing is to compensate to get
those rigs
[Music]
three
oh
[Music]
okay
so now you fill it up with water
you're trying to start it
yeah
you don't want to know too much then
you've got small battery what
here we go
[Music]
all right okay so
there we are that's the situation
now the next trick
the next trick
the next trick is to um
next trick is to
turn the um
take the thing
making a good
connection
electrical connections there yeah
now this here goes to the power to the
cell yes
you know you follow those wires you'll
find that the wire comes from that fuse
to the switch
gives me power to the end of that
[Music]
discharged the battery
farther myself so i'll just make that
clear
so once these guys get equipped i'll
change my battery in my camera and here
we are just backing up the battery in
the back
better
can you put your hands up
okay
[Music]
now this is running on h particles
absolutely
okay so we're all going to go for ride
and just before we do that can i smell
these though
[Music]
yes
it does have some contaminants but
totally
[Music]
[Laughter]
now
just before we head
off we're now totally on our height
particle yes we get vr this is wonderful
okay
you can come back a bit
now i hope my
you notice that the motor is running
smoothly just a minute yeah i just put
this on standby and put my suit board on
[Music]
okay um
see that battery charger over there the
camera recharges here those two
batteries all for me so i can put them
[Music]
we don't want to run out of fuel battery
fuel now do we
just yeah just on that charger
just slide them off
yeah that just pull the batteries off
the side
now the batteries are on the side of
that that you had sure
go back yeah
pull them up
voila
okay
as we're saying we're filing about 1100
rpm
compared to where we were
the fuel cell comes down here
okay as she goes down see
yeah
now we're still putting electrical
energy into this now correctly
[Music]
go ahead to the other one
the cell is now still being driven by
electrical energy roughly how many amps
would you say
yeah wouldn't be two
quarters
[Music]
now i'll reiterate again we are running
h particle no hydrocarbon fuel at all
zero
[Music]
talk to me
half of water in and found that he
overfilled it
because there's not meant to be in it
okay we're still running electricity at
the moment decor
until we get it fully cleared up and
running
[Music]
yeah i mean i'm going to be on my level
okay
[Music]
all right
[Applause]
come on yeah the yeah
yesterday
yes there is you want to look what
no
magic
there's something there to see
it doesn't show